axparis.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy – AX Paris

Privacy matters AXPARIS recognizes the importance of our customers' privacy and takes a number of steps to protect that privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for our web site.

AX PARIS believes in protecting the privacy of its customers. The purpose of this privacy policy is to describe the kinds of information that we may gather about you; how we may use that information; how we protect it; when we may disclose it; and the choices you have regarding your information.

By visiting the site, you are consenting to the practices described in the current version of this privacy policy. If you have visited the site previously, please review the privacy policy again to be sure you are familiar with its present terms. Recent changes to the privacy policy can be found below under Privacy Policy Changes.

If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy or security of your information, you may contact us.

**Non-Personal Information that We Collect**

We automatically collect non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit our Site. This information includes your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. This number does not identify your name, email address, or other personal information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site.

We also collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of cookies. A cookie is an alphanumeric file that a web site puts on your hard drive so that it can remember something about you while you are using the site or when you return to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to use our site. We use a cookie in order to retain the contents in your shopping cart while you are checking out other areas on our site. When you are done, the products in your cart are still there for you to buy. We also use cookies to gather certain aggregate usage information about the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and individual pages of our site. This data helps us improve the appearance and usability of the Site. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information nor do we combine information collected through these cookies with other personally identifiable information about you.

**Personal Information that We Collect**

We ask for your name, telephone number, home address, email address and age for competitions, prize draws or newsletter sign ups. When a purchase is made on our site, in addition to the above, we also ask for delivery address, and payment method details. We may obtain information about your usage of our web site to help us develop and improve it further.

**Uses of your Information**

Financial information that is collected is used to bill you for products that you request. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to you. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see "How to remove your name from our mailing, sharing or email list" below.

If you register for email or if you provide your email address to us, we will send you emails. These emails will inform you of our launch of new products. If you currently receive our emails and do not wish to continue receiving them, please see the "How to remove your name from our mailing, sharing or email list" section below.

We use your shipping address to ship your products to you and to send catalogues and other mailings to you. We use your billing address, if different than your shipping address, to verify your billing information. We never share our customer names or addresses, e-mail addresses or other personally identifiable information, other than to the extent described in the “Consenting to Uses of Your Information” section below. If you do not wish to receive catalogues or other mailings from us, please see the "How to remove your name from our mailing, sharing or email list" section below.

**Payment**

In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.

General information on Klarna you can find [here](https://www.klarna.com/uk/). Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in[ Klarna’s privacy policy](http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy).

**Disclosures of Your Information**

We do not disclose your personal information to other companies, persons or agencies.

**How to Remove your Name from Our Mailing, Sharing or Email List**

Our Site provides you the choice to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you.

**Remove**

Our Site gives you the following options for removing your information from our database to not receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service, or to not share your name and address with other companies.

1\. You may send an email to

**Protection of Personal Information**

We want you to feel confident about using AXPARIS to make purchases and we are committed to protecting the personal information we collect. While no web site can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial security procedures to help protect the personal information that you provide to us.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

AXPARIS may update this privacy policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this privacy policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our web site.

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy or security of your information, you may contact us in any of the following ways.

1\. You may contact us on our support area below

**EFFECTIVE DATE 1st April 2008**
